RAJAS NADKARNI

PGDM (MBA): Marketing (Majors), Operation (Minors)
Graduation: Bachelor of Engineering, Electrical and Electronics

7 years of experience in Digital Marketing with core competency in Brand Marketing and proficient understanding of Performance Marketing, Corporate Communication, Product Marketing and Online Reputation Management.

Note: Available for immediate joining

SKILLS

- Brand Management
- Corporate Communication
- Strategic Planning and Media buying Digital & Traditional Media
- Social Media Marketing, SEO, SEM, Lead Generation
- Project Management

- Online Reputation Management Brand sentiment management
- Digital Marketing Tools Social Studio by Salesforce, Hootsuite, Radarly, Leadsquared Lead Management, Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, Facebook Business Manager

WORK EXPERIENCE		
Kurl-on Enterprise Limited, Bangalore October 2018 -September 2020		
Profile	Product Marketing Manager – Sofa & Furniture	
Responsibilities	 Responsible for Marketing, Sales and Product Life Cycle Management for e-Commerce Business Strategize and execute digital marketing activities – SEO/SEM/Programmatic – with partner agencies to achieve business objective Create communication briefs for campaign content and product catalogue 	
Highlights	 35% growth in furniture division FY19-20, 140% growth in e-Commerce business Introduction of 80+ SKUs of Kurl-on Sofa & Furniture on Flipkart Marketplace 	
Additional responsibilities	Managed Google Business Manager for Kurl-on's "Company Owned Company Operated" retail stores	

1to1help.net, Ban	galore April 2018-October 2018
Profile	B2B Marketing Manager
Responsibilities	 Manage brand communications and marketing to increase brand awareness and engagement by creating appropriate content Generating leads through performance marketing on LinkedIn, Programmatic, SEM/SEO and other plats, and nurture it to increase conversion rates Website & CRM portal management
Highlights	 Streamlined digital performance marketing to reduce lead acquisition cost by 90% Increased conversion rate by 30%

SBI Life Insurance Co Ltd, Head Office-Mumbai April 2016– March 2018		
Profile	Manager-Social Media & Digital Marketing and Online Reputation Management, Brand and Corporate Communication	
Responsibilities	 Social Media & Digital Marketing Strategize, plan and execute social media and digital marketing activities to increase brand awareness and engagement on the basis of Hero-Hub-Hygiene model. Set annual digital marketing KPIs for the brand along with budgetary allocation to various platforms in accordance to business objectives Managing new product launches on digital media by creating necessary content for digital marketing platforms in collaboration with product team, compliance and other stakeholders. Manage online product communication and campaign content for performance marketing. 	

Mail: rajas.pn@gmail.com Mobile: +91-7506647677 10 September 2020

	 Collaborate with CSR and PR team to create and disseminate content to increase brand reputation on digital media. Covering live events and seminars with MD&CEO participation on social media. Online Reputation Management - Managing a team of two Monitor brand mentions and take actions according the keyword sentiments Manage response management on Social Media for customer/distributor grievances and queries within specified TAT.
	 Co-ordinate with State Bank of India, BNP Paribas Cardiff and other group subsidiaries to manage group level online sentiment.
Highlights	 Setup brand guidelines and communication protocols for all digital communication, including campaigns, social media & internal and external stakeholder code of conduct. Increased SBI Life's Social Media presence by more than 3x across Social Media Channels with consistent average engagement rate of 5% during campaigns Set up process to streamline annual, quarterly, monthly and weekly activities on digital marketing and social media. Internal process set up for Online Reputation Management (ORM) to ensure TAT of less than 4 hours in a regulatory environment. Established annual content properties on social media such as for #PapaHainNa for Father's Day, #PlanToCelebrate for various festivals, #DilBacchaTohSabAccha for Children's Day
Recognition	Received GEM - <i>Going Extra Mile</i> Award for initiatives in Digital for FY 2016-17.

SBI Life Insuranc	e Co Ltd, Head Office-Mumbai April 2013– March 2016	
Profile	Assistant Marketing Manager - Brand and Corporate Communication	
Responsibilities	 Planning and execution of Digital & Social Media campaigns – Content creation and Promotional activities Managing Online Reputation management – Sentiment analysis and CRM Product Communication - Managed product communication (Online & Offline) for 12 most selling products of SBI Life. Execution of TV, Radio, Airport Advertising campaigns. Responsible for Implementing IRDAI mandated Insurance Awareness Program in Tripura, Mizoram and Pondicherry through Mass Media, Sponsorships, Events and Direct Marketing 	
Highlights	 Campaign Awards #GreatDad FY 2014-15: A special engagement campaign based on SBI Life's Great Dad TVC. The campaign received multiple awards including IndiaAA and Prime Awards Conceptualised communication route for six new products during FY 2014-16. 	

MBA, GOA INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT

June 2011 - March 2013

PRE-MBA WORK EXPERIENCE

ABB India Ltd

July 2009 – October 2010

- Sales and Marketing Engineer, Small Power Transformer Unit Vadodara, Management Trainee
- Commissioning and Designing Engineer at ABB India Ltd, in Process Automation- Cement Division Bangalore, Management Trainee

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Summer Internship at Micro Labs Ltd., Executed Line Balancing as Summer Project

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES			
Software(s)	MS Excel, MS Word, MS Power Point, Office 365		
Certifications	 Goldratt Certificate of Achievement in TOC Business Innovation Level 3 Search Engine Optimisation Specialisation from UC Davis via Coursera 		

Mail: rajas.pn@gmail.com Mobile: +91-7506647677 10 September 2020

ACADEMIC DISTINCTIONS/CERTIFICATIONS

Award(s) Achieved3rd Place in Capstone International Challenge Fall 2012.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS				
Exam / Degree	Board / University	Year	Percentage	Grade/Equivalent
PGDM	Goa Institute of Management	2013	5.33/8	В
BE	Goa Engineering College, Goa University	2009	65.3	First Class
Std. XII	Goa Board of Secondary And Hr. Secondary Edu.	2005	74	First Class
Std. X	Goa Board of Secondary And Hr.	2003	82.3	Distinction

ACADEMIC PRO	<u>IECTS</u>
Goa Institute of Management	 Created "Communication Strategy for Frugurt-Yogurt" as a part of Integrated Marketing Communication Course.
	 Assisted "Chorao Farmers Club, Goa" to Expand their Retail Sales Area of Farm Products, eliminating Middle Man and increasing Farmers Margin, as
	a part of Corporate Social Responsibility at GIM

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY/ PERSONAL INITIATIVES		
Goa Institute of Management	 Core Committee Member, Industry Institute Interaction Club-Club provides students opportunities to work on Live Industry Projects 	
	Member of Sponsorship and Logistics Team of Samriddhi 2011 and 2012	
Goa Engineering College	 Public Relationship Officer, Student Council(2008) 	
	 Executive Member of ELECTRA(E&E club) for four consecutive years 	
	 Initiated Intra-College cultural festival, "Tandav" 	

EXTRACURRICULAR ATIVITIES DURING ACADEMIC YEARS		
Awards	NCC Army(2 Years), B-Certificate, Rank: Lance Corporal	
	NCC Navy(3 Years), A-Certificate	
Sports	Represented School at State Level Badminton Competition	
Others	Participated in National Science Exhibition(2004-05)	

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES			
Interests	World History, Geo Politics, Geography, Consumer Psychology		
Hobbies	 Travelling, Cycling, Hiking and Camping Cooking Reading – Fiction, Sci-Fi, History. Favourite books include The Lord of The Rings, How Brands Grow, August Guns 		

PERSONAL INFORMATION	
Notice Period	Not Applicable. Available for immediate joining.
Language(s)	Konkani, English, Hindi, Marathi
Date of Birth	10 th December 1987
Phone	+91 7506647677
Mail ID	rajas.pn@gmail.com
Permanent Address	AS1, Orchid Green Apartment Alto Duler Mapusa Goa, 403 507
Current Address	Bangalore, Karnataka. Open for relocation.

Mail: rajas.pn@gmail.com Mobile: +91-7506647677 10 September 2020